HI removed, cleaned
and corrected by Lunar Team
Blow out the candles
and make a wish.
Okay.
Is that it?
- All right.
- Okay.
At last, the presents.
- Is it a vase?
Oh, wait, Jane's gonna guess.
- Thanks.
- Okay, Jane.
Yoga mat?
- Correct.
- Ha, ha, ha.
We talked about that ashtanga class.
I just thought...
- It's great. Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- Ten bucks says you don't get this one.
- You're on. Ten bucks.
- Hmm?
- Happy birthday.
- Cover your eyes.
- Got it.
- Don't cheat.
- No cheating.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Clear?
- Okay, Jane.
- Okay, Rigsby.
It's a gift certificate
for a spa treatment.
- Damn.
- Correct again.
- Bingo. Ten dollars?
- Yeah, I owe you.
Aw.
Okay, two for two. How about mine?
- Uh, Cho.
- That's sweet, thank you.
- I got it.
- Okay.
Okay, what is it?
It's, uh,
a mid-to high-end bottle of...
...wine...
Uh, no, no, no. Unh.
Champagne.
- Yes.
- Ha, ha, ha. Yup, there I go.
- Regift?
- It's a really good bottle. I don't drink it.
- Ah, let's have some cake.
- Okay.
What about your gift?
It's on its way.
Oh.
Typical.
You really think
I would forget your birthday present?
- Van Pelt.
- It's on its way.
Yeah, right.
Little grumpy because
Daddy didn't buy you a pony?
Boss, we got a call.
Couple of hikers
found him this morning.
Looks like he's been out here
a couple of days.
Gunshot to the forehead.
There's no ID.
This is all we found on him.
A straw tube and, uh,
I don't know, religious medal?
- A good luck charm, maybe?
- Didn't work too well, if it was.
Our victim worked in a video arcade...
- ...in the next town to the north.
- How do you get that?
Big storm here last week,
wasn't there?
Lot of rain.
Snow up in the mountains.
When the river rises,
this must be underwater.
He must have been brought
from upriver...
- ...and got caught in the tree.
- Okay. What about the arcade?
Well, this is a token
used for video games.
And this is a Peruvian finger cuff.
They give them away as cheap prizes.
Our man looks a little old to be
hanging out in a video game arcade.
Unless he's into kids.
Doesn't look the type.
I bet he works in one.
We find the arcade,
we find the information.
- What's the next big town upriver?
- Sierra Vista.
Okay, it's a theory.
We're done. He's all yours.
Uh, do I detect a slight residue
of grumpiness in your demeanor?
No.
I swear to you, Lisbon,
your gift is on its way.
I'm not grumpy, and I don't give a damn
about your supposed gift.
- She's still grumpy with me, isn't she?
- Huh. Not touching that.
This is the only arcade in town.
And only
a couple miles from the river.
Gasoline, cheese, mesquite.
It's wonderful. This is the place.
We'll see.
Oh, hey, you got a dollar on you?
I'll give it right back.
Ah!
Bingo.
Well, okay. You're right.
Ah.
Here you go. Have fun.
Wow. Wow, that's Ed Didrikson.
He's been working for me
about two years.
- Okay.
- What happened?
Somebody killed him.
Can you think why that would happen?
No, he kept to himself, mostly.
No trouble. No trouble at all.
An honest, reliable,
married-man type guy.
- Wife's name?
- Uh, don't recall. Uh.
Karen, Carol, something like that.
And
what was his position here exactly?
Shift manager.
Ran the till, kept the kids in line.
He was good at that.
It's a responsible position.
- Any money go missing lately?
- Nope. And I keep tabs, trust me.
And why should we trust you?
Uh, it... It's just a phrase,
uh, like "you know."
- What do I know?
- No. Uh, you don't know anything,
- I'm saying it's just a thing to say.
- Oh, it's a figure of speech.
Uh-huh.
- So we shouldn't trust you really.
- Yeah. No, you should.
When was the last time
you saw Didrikson?
Friday night when he left work.
He didn't show up for work next day.
I called his home, there was no answer.
Next day, his wife was there...
...said he was away
on a, uh, family emergency.
- Doesn't know when he'll be back.
- An emergency?
That's all she said.
How was her tone?
Was she calm or was she upset?
Upset, I guess.
- We'll need the home address.
- Sure thing.
- Now.
- Right.
If you wouldn't mind.
- Huh. Kind of hard to trust the guy.
- Yup.
You and Rigsby stay here,
talk to the kids Didrikson kept in line.
See if they have the same take.
Cho, Van Pelt and I...
- ...are gonna talk to the wife.
- All right.
- Bye.
Teenagers. I hate questioning teenagers.
It's like talking to mud.
- You need some love in your heart.
- Oh, is that my problem?
Yeah, it is.
- Stay close.
- Great.
Hmm.
Not bad. Not bad at all. Wanna see
how it's supposed to be done?
- What are you, sex perverts or cops?
- See what I mean?
Oh, he's a cop.
I'm just a concerned citizen.
- All right. We got nothing to say to you.
- Yeah, screw the cops.
Even for a midget villain like you,
that's an untenable position.
Every modern society
has some kind of police force.
It's like saying,
"Screw the public transport system."
Oh.
Thank you.
What'd you find out?
County tax collectors list the owners
as Ed and Jenny Didrikson.
Moved here two years ago from Texas.
No kids, no criminal records.
Not much of anything,
as far as the data goes.
Only odd thing is they paid
for the house in cash, no mortgage.
- That's crazy. How'd you do that?
- Focus.
Watch as I make this machine
do my bidding.
Do exactly as I tell you.
You. Take over.
You, come with me.
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
So...
...tell us what you know
about Ed Didrikson.
- Eddie that works here?
- Mm-hm.
I mean, Eddie's a cool guy.
- He'll hook you up if he knows you.
- Hook you up? With what?
Uh, weed, you know.
It's Tiny's stuff, but...
- Tiny?
- Yeah, he's a biker.
He rolls with the X's.
It's his stuff, same price.
He doesn't mess with people
like Tiny does. You could borrow money.
Charges a heavy vig,
but that's all right.
- Didrikson calls it a vig?
- Am I not saying it right? Vig?
- Is he saying it wrong?
- That's right.
That's right.
Anything else you can tell us?
He was always talking about respect.
He won't tolerate any kind of dis.
This one time,
Slow Ritchie gave him the finger.
He reached out and broke it.
- You could hear the bone crack.
- Ouch.
Ritchie's on the floor screaming.
Did looks at him cold,
cusses him out in French...
- ...and goes about his business.
- In French?
- I don't know. Something foreign.
- Interesting.
Do you know he's dead?
- Eddie?
- Yeah.
No. What happened?
Thanks for your help.
You can go now.
Back door's locked as well.
Feels like a deadbolt.
Somebody's watching us
from the upstairs window.
Jenny Didrikson? CBI. Police.
Let us in.
We'd like to speak with you.
We don't have time to wait
for a warrant.
But we do have reason to believe
that somebody's life is in danger, right?
Mrs. Didrikson?
Get out of my house,
you murdering scum.
I swear to God, I'll blow you away.
Mrs. Didrikson,
I'm gonna show you my badge.
I got people coming.
You better get out of here.
Mrs. Didrikson, we're with
the California Bureau of Investigation.
- Put the gun down.
- California Bureau of My Ass.
You get the hell out of here.
I will shoot you.
This is my cell phone.
I'm gonna dial 911...
...and we will get
uniformed policemen here.
They will sort everything out.
In the meantime, we'll all relax.
Screw you!
I'm gonna count to 10,
and then I'm gonna start shooting.
One,
two...
- Lisbon.
- Jane, get off the phone.
- ...three...
- I think I know what we have here.
- ...four...
- I've got a situation.
- ...five, six...
- Didrikson used to work for the Mob.
- ...seven...
- He went into witness protection.
...eight...
Freeze! Don't move!
Drop your weapons.
Get on the ground, hands on your heads.
Who are you people?
We're with the
California Bureau of Investigation.
I'm Agent Lisbon.
These are Agents Cho and Van Pelt.
- We're U.S. Marshals.
- Yeah, we can see that.
Okay, fellas, stand down.
Jenny?
Jenny, it's us.
Whoa.
Sweetheart, put the gun down.
It's okay.
All right.
Sorry, agent.
I didn't mean to scare you.
You know, we hear the bell,
we come running.
That's all right. We weren't scared.
No hard feelings, right?
Come on down, Jenny. It's all right.
All right, so why are you here?
What did Eddie do now?
He's dead.
Single shot to the forehead.
- We found him 15 miles downriver.
- Damn.
- I knew this would happen.
- You didn't know he was missing...
- ...and he was under your protection?
- Jenny informed us three days ago.
He's been AWOL before. We figured
he was on another drunk or something.
You sons of bitches. I told you
they'd get him! I told you, you bastards!
Bastards!
Wow, what'd I miss?
Until two years ago,
Ed Didrikson was Eddie Russo
from Philadelphia.
He ran numbers for the Battaglia family.
And loan sharking and collections.
Got caught with 10 kilos of cocaine.
The Feds flipped him.
The guy actually testified against
Santino Battaglia and his family.
The old man didn't go down,
but two of his sons got life.
Russo and wife moved out here
under our supervision...
...with the Witness Relocation Program.
So, what do you think happened here?
What went wrong?
Same old story, I guess.
People can't resist contacting
someone back home, from their old life.
That person tells somebody.
Somebody sells him out...
...to Santino Battaglia.
You know, it happens.
We tell them again and again,
"Your old life is dead, gone. Forget it."
But, uh, they don't listen.
- You are Witness Protection, right?
- Yeah.
You're supposed to protect people?
We're not bodyguards, agent.
We don't babysit people.
Consultant. She's the agent.
I'm the consultant.
- Agent.
- You were saying?
- Consultant?
- Mm-hm.
Okay. We physically meet
with our clients once a week.
Last appointment with Eddie
was the day before he disappeared.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Jenny told you he was missing.
- You did nothing?
- What should we have done?
Alerted the media? We were looking.
Like I said, it wasn't the first time Eddie
jumped the fence. This isn't our fault.
Oh. Did you know that
Eddie was dealing drugs?
- No.
- Yeah.
Selling marijuana and pills to children.
- No. Where did you get that?
- Kid down at the arcade...
...said he was fronting for a biker
named Tiny.
You guys have been busy, huh?
Yeah.
Just to be clear, you didn't know...
...about any criminal activities
the victim might have engaged in?
He was a Mafioso. It's not like
he's gonna join the church choir.
So you did know?
- No. We didn't.
- No.
Nor do we now.
You wanna know something?
This is starting to sound
an awful lot like an interrogation.
Not appreciated.
We have reports to write.
It was very nice to have met you.
Do you prefer Gina or Jenny?
Who gives a damn?
Call me what you like.
Gina, then.
When did you last see your husband?
It was last Friday morning.
He never came home from work.
He called that afternoon, said he had
business to do, that he'd be home late.
That was the last time
I heard from him.
What kind of business?
I don't know. Business. I didn't ask.
- You didn't ask or didn't wanna know?
- Oh, I get it. He's a bad man, right?
Must have been doing something wrong.
He's out there raping and killing.
- Must have deserved what he got, huh?
- Gina.
What's he gonna do wrong
in this place?
- Vandalize a cactus?
- You don't like it here?
You know what the worst part is?
The food.
They got no good red sauce, no sausage,
and they put pineapple on their pizza.
Hmm.
You have any idea
who might have done this?
Who do you think?
That pig, Sonny Battaglia,
and his people.
They swore they'd get my husband.
Now they have.
My husband did the right thing,
didn't he?
He did what his country
asked him to do.
So why is it that they didn't take care
of us like they were supposed to?
Did you or your husband talk to anyone
from the old days, your previous life?
- No. What, are we idiots? No.
- Who do you talk to?
Yeah, right. Who?
I talk to no one.
The wind.
So how would the Battaglias
have found out where you were located?
It was the marshals, of course.
Somebody paid one of those WitSec
sons of bitches to rat us out.
Gina, look at me.
Whoever did this, we will catch them.
I promise.
Okay.
- What did you learn?
- She's scared. She's of Italian descent.
She bites her nails.
She doesn't like pets or pineapple.
Useful stuff.
Cho, reach out
to the Organized Crime Unit.
Get a line on Sonny Battaglia.
Find out who's in charge...
...who they might hire
to do something like this.
You and Rigsby go and find Tiny.
Bring him in.
Do we know who he rides with?
Kids did say something
about him being with the X's.
I know a guy in San Berdoo
has a CI with them.
We'll find Tiny, no problem.
- Hey, we're closed.
- Is one of you Tiny?
Who's asking?
We're with the
California Bureau of Investigation.
Hey...!
Get out of here before
I call your parole officers.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
- You got me!
- Sorry.
- All right?
- Yeah.
- Let's put him in the chair.
- Okay.
We just wanted
to ask you some questions.
I don't like cops.
Ed Didrikson was found dead yesterday.
What do you know about that?
Who's Ed Didrikson?
You were in business with Ed,
dealing marijuana.
Mari-what?
We just wanna find out who killed him.
Help us with that...
...we don't care
about your other business.
Eddie was a rat.
Rats get dead.
Not by me. Not by me.
- But it happens. Nobody likes rats.
- He ratted you out?
Couple weeks back, Eddie and me
were in his car, doing business.
We got busted by a Sierra Vista P.D.,
holding 10 pounds of weed.
I'm in the tank two days.
I go before the judge, and it's just me.
Eddie's gone. And I mean gone.
He's not even on the docket anymore.
He's off the original arrest report.
- So, what does that tell you?
- Obviously he's a narc.
Or a snitch.
And he's so well connected...
...he don't mind that
I know that's what he is.
Dirty, lowdown scum.
That don't mean I killed him.
Sierra Vista P.D. confirmed...
...that John "Tiny" Callaghan
was arrested two weeks ago...
...on marijuana charges.
They say he was alone.
Not with Eddie Didrikson.
They don't know anything about him.
What about records for the vehicle
Tiny was busted in?
No vehicle.
He was stopped on the street.
Walking around
with 10 pounds of marijuana.
That's what the chief says.
- What did he sound like?
- Like he was covering for some guy.
- We need to speak to those marshals.
- I'm gonna make that call.
Any word on Sonny Battaglia?
After his two sons went to prison,
Sonny Battaglia retired.
Left the business
to his number two, Joseph Angelini.
So Angelini would only want to send
Eddie Russo his best wishes.
- Battaglia would want him dead.
- He's out of the business.
Pushing 70. Plays golf in Palm Desert.
People say he's not retired...
- ...just playing it that way to keep clean.
- Palm Desert right here in California?
- No.
- Palm Desert's not in California?
No, you can't sneak off
and talk to Sonny Battaglia.
Oh, I thought you meant Palm Desert
wasn't in California.
It is in California, right?
- Son of a...! In the trees again.
- Excuse me.
Sonny Battaglia?
- Keep moving, Jack.
- Name's Jane.
Patrick Jane.
- I need a moment of your time, if I may.
- For what?
Speak about Eddie Russo.
- You a cop?
- Ha, ha, no.
Good. You alone?
Yeah.
Shoot him.
Ooh.
There's three reasons I'm not scared.
Well, okay, I'm scared. But there's
three reasons I'm not terrified.
Please, tell.
One, you don't get to be your age,
rich, unimprisoned...
...by shooting people willy-nilly
on golf courses.
Until now.
- You know what consistency is?
- The hobgoblin of little minds.
Right. Emerson.
Okay. Reason number two?
I can significantly improve
your golf game.
You and a hundred other baccalàs.
Reason number three.
I know where to find Eddie Russo.
- How do I improve my game?
- Well, it's very simple.
You have to think of hitting
the ball more as an act of creation.
What you need is a little more flow.
- Flow?
- Mm-hm.
- I changed my mind. Shoot him.
- What's your favorite song?
- You're the smartass, you tell me.
- It's either Elvis, Sinatra or Italian opera.
Enrico Caruso singing "Santa Lucia."
Perfect. Hand me one of those sticks.
We'll get started.
- Sticks?
- Whatever you call them.
Not the fat one. Get the other kind.
Okay. Well, that's a little fat,
but we'll make it work.
Flow.
- Thanks for coming.
- What's the deal?
- We don't have much time.
- Have a seat in my office. It's quieter.
- You remember Agent Cho.
- How you doing?
I won't beat around the bush.
Two weeks ago, did you get Eddie Russo
off the hook for a drug bust?
No, we did not.
Somebody did, and it made
his accomplice very angry at him.
- Why would we do that?
- Maybe you had a deal with Russo.
He gets to deal drugs,
and you look the other way...
...or even help him,
as long as he keeps helping the feds.
Let me explain the real world
to you, Teresa.
Russo's been squeezed dry
of testimony.
Prosecutors don't need him. They don't
care what happens, and neither do we.
He gets busted, that's his problem.
And it's less work for us.
So either the local cops
were in business with Eddie...
...or, my guess,
you're just as misinformed...
...as you are disrespectful and dumb.
Bye now.
- Seems dirty, doesn't he?
- Yep.
Why don't you check with IA about him
and his partner. See if anything pops.
Where's Jane?
Don't get mad.
He went down to talk to Battaglia.
Damn it.
Should one of us head down
to Palm Desert just in case?
He made his bed.
I should've shot you myself
when you showed up.
All the hours I spent on this course.
The thousands I wasted on videotapes
and coaching.
And blondie here, he does it
with singing. How do you like that, huh?
I'm just polishing the
talent that was already there.
Yeah. Yeah.
So now tell me, my strange new friend.
Where is Eddie Russo?
- You didn't know?
- Know what?
Eddie Russo's dead.
No kidding.
Killed. A couple of days ago.
He's in the state morgue in Sacramento
under the name of Ed Didrikson.
Who did it?
You don't know? Interesting.
- Who did it?
- I don't know.
- Today is a good day.
- Good.
Listen, if you ever find out
who killed Eddie, you call me, okay?
I wanna send whoever did it
some flowers and a thank-you note.
Sure. What's your number?
What are you doing?
Don't give him your number.
This guy? What is he gonna do?
- Here. It's a clean line. You can talk.
- Thank you.
So if you didn't do it, then who
would've done it? Who was next in line?
An angry husband, most likely.
Eddie was a degenerate skirt hound.
- Is that right?
- Hmm.
An animal. Compulsive.
So tell me, uh, how was it done?
How did they do it to him?
Oh, uh, I can assure you, he...
He didn't suffer.
Thanks for your time, Mr. Battaglia.
See you later.
- I'm not finished talking yet.
- I'm finished talking with you.
What are you, Al Pacino all of a sudden?
People don't act that way with me.
I do when there's witnesses around.
What are we gonna do?
He's got a screw loose.
You think you have an outlaw charm
about you, and you do.
But you live by oppression.
In reality, you're just a greedy,
twisted little sadist.
Hey, screw you, blondie.
You're lucky you helped me
beat Arnold Palmer here...
...or I'd plug you right now.
To hell with the witnesses.
Screw you.
You played golf with Sonny Battaglia?
Yeah. Sonny, uh...
Well, I did. Mm-hm.
- And what'd you learn?
- He didn't kill Russo.
- And golf is oddly very easy.
- And you're sure of this?
Hmm. I'm very sure. It's all about
rhythm. Anyone could do it.
Yeah, Sonny Battaglia's clean.
It's hard to say with a sociopath.
Doesn't mean some other Mafioso
didn't do it.
Sonny thinks it was an ex-lover.
The key is who sprung Eddie.
I'm betting it's those marshals.
We're gonna have to accuse
the Sierra Vista P.D. of double-dealing.
A vehicle registered to Ed Didrikson
just entered the system.
It was towed from the lot
outside House of Games.
Sierra Vista P.D.
couldn't find their ass in the dark.
So if Russo's car
was outside House of Games...
...somebody picked him up.
Maybe the arcade security cameras
have a picture.
- Why don't you two find out.
- Right.
Yeah, you guys go find out.
I'll find the couch.
Oh, there it is.
- We need to look at your security tapes.
- Tapes? I have no tapes.
- You have cameras.
- Of course.
But only the little red light works.
That's all you need.
What are you guys looking for?
Nothing happened here.
We wanna know
who picked up Russo.
I could tell you. His wife.
I saw her in the parking lot.
- His wife?
- Yeah.
- You sure it was her?
- Sure. I mean, I assume it was her.
She's picked him up
a couple times before.
- Brunette, slim, maybe 5'4"?
- No. A pretty black lady, about 5'10".
Boss, we're gonna need to speak
to Marshal Knox about a few things.
Mm-hm.
Hey. What do you people
think you're playing at?
- Who's your supervisor?
- Oh, uh.
- I want some answers right now.
- Uh, Lisbon.
I'm gonna make you regret
you ever screwed with me.
- I'm not a cop.
- Hello, Marshal Exley.
I got a call from my supervisor
telling me that you put in a request...
...to question Marshal Knox as
a person of interest in the Russo case.
- Yes.
- It's all over the department.
- Why are you trying to ruin her?
- Did you know she was with Russo...
- ...the night he vanished?
- So you're saying she fingered him?
- That she set him up for the mob?
- Looks that way.
No, that's garbage. It's absurd.
I would've known.
- Just saying.
- She's my partner, for God's sake.
- I would know if she wasn't straight.
- We confirmed with the Sierra Vista P.D.
The night Russo got arrested,
Knox had them drop the charges...
...as if she was doing it
on behalf of the Marshal Service.
Why would she do that?
Well, there's no use in fingering Russo
if he's locked up safe in prison.
No, this is a mistake.
There's some explanation.
Then why can't we find her
to hear her say that?
I don't know.
- Do you know where she is now?
- No.
All right, then.
Ma'am?
Hello?
She's hardly breathing.
Better call it in.
Two Alpha 44,
I need fire and rescue to roll Code 3...
...to the 500 block of Lexington.
Attempted suicide.
Got it. Thanks.
She's at County General.
They're pumping her stomach now.
Is she gonna be okay?
They don't know what she took
or how much. It's early...
- ...but it looks like she's gonna make it.
- Okay.
I'm gonna go see her.
- Wait. We'll come with.
- No, that's all right. I can handle this.
I respect your distress,
she's your partner...
...but please understand
our situation here.
We've got a case,
and she's still a person of interest.
- We need to speak to her.
- Okay. I understand.
- You've got a job to do.
- Oh, here's a thought.
- What if you did it?
- Me? What?
Sure. Knox wasn't setting up
Russo with the mob.
She was meeting him
because they were having an affair.
- That makes sense.
- It does. Doesn't it?
- You're out of your mind.
- That crook in bed with your Christy?
Don't tell us
you don't have a crush on her.
- That's crap, pal.
- Uh, you see the anger?
That could screw up your career,
along with hers.
Any man in your position
would wanna kill him.
- That's enough.
- I'm not saying that you knew.
I'm just saying that if you did,
you'd be our prime suspect.
Your best defense is your apparent
lack of the most basic detective skills.
Oh, you little son of a bitch.
I'm sorry. I'm just thinking aloud.
No offense.
- Yeah, right. No offense.
- None taken.
Well, you certainly pushed his buttons,
didn't you?
Eh.
Cho, come to the hospital with me.
You two talk to Gina Russo.
Find out what she thinks about all this.
- Try and behave yourself.
- I'll do my best.
- Can I see your phone?
- Do you think he did it? Exley?
I don't know. Do you think he did it?
Well, if there was an affair,
he had motive, like you said.
Yeah, if.
Didn't respond well to being prodded.
- Nobody does.
- When someone answers...
- ...can you say, "Is Mary there?"
- Why?
Just for fun.
Huh.
- Hi. Is, um... Is Mary there?
- No, lady. It's the wrong number.
- Wrong number. What was that about?
- Groundwork.
Could I have a look at your phone?
Here. Hold these.
Try them on.
Wow, they look good.
Do you have, uh, whatchamacallit,
uh, warm-up gear, training sweats?
- The shiny type?
- No. Yep. Where are you going with this?
- Ask to speak to Mary.
- I don't like this.
- Hi, can I speak to Mary, please?
- No.
- What did they say?
- No. Heh, heh.
- Who was that?
- Old friend. Where's your sweat gear?
- Uh, in my locker.
- All right, let's go.
Jane?
- Here we go.
- Okay.
But I'd feel better
if Lisbon knew about this.
So tell her.
- You know what to do, right?
- Mm-hm.
Stay a few minutes
until she gets comfortable...
...then when Rigsby calls, you leave.
- What's my reason for leaving?
- Doesn't matter. Just be vague.
Rigsby's right, you know.
Lisbon told us to go see Gina Russo.
She told you to stay out of trouble.
- Sonny, hi. Patrick Jane.
- Oh, yeah. You.
Okay. You got a name for me?
No, not yet. Maybe soon.
Never mind about that.
Mary wants to know,
has anyone left any messages for her?
Are you crazy?
Listen, you jerk.
I will tear your freaking head off...
...and stick it where the sun don't...
You gotta talk to the marshals for me.
I wanna know when I'm gonna get moved.
- Uh, that's not really our purview, but...
- Thank you. I'd appreciate it.
What's he doing?
Oh, uh, you said you can't get any
good food out here...
...so, uh, I thought I'd come by
and cook you some.
Huh.
If you wanna help,
you can chop these.
Okay.
Do you have an apron?
I can't imagine being out here
in the desert alone...
...with the coyotes and the tumbleweeds
and the bad red sauce.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Out here, you're all alone.
When you were homesick, Eddie
probably told you to make friends...
- ...join a gym or something, right?
- Yoga, he says.
Ah, yoga.
Standing on your head, listening
to flute music's definitely the answer.
Yeah?
Okay. Got it.
I've gotta go do something. Work.
Oh, well, come back quick.
We'll still be here.
All right. Bye.
Mmm. Mmm.
- Mm. That was good.
- Hm, not bad at all.
We believe Eddie was having a romantic
relationship with Christy Knox...
...from the Witsec Program.
Romantic?
With the marshal lady?
Are you kidding?
No. Never happened. No.
Why are you so sure?
Eddie liked the ladies, right? Didn't he?
Womanizer. Famous for it.
Yeah, maybe in his old life.
But he changed.
Changed? Really? You believe
that people can change who they are?
- Yeah. Sure. People can change.
- Eddie couldn't change. No.
He used to be somebody.
Now he's gotta be nobody.
No. Even after he dragged you
all the way out here...
...to the middle of nowhere, there's
still nights he doesn't come home.
Just like before.
Before you can move on, Gina,
you're gonna make things right now.
Tell me the truth.
I'm not saying nothing.
You found out he was cheating,
you snapped, shot him.
Say whatever you like.
It means nothing.
- You have to prove it.
- Where'd you do it?
What happened to the gun
that you used?
You want some coffee? Dessert?
No, thanks.
The reason I'm here alone...
...my colleagues
are kind of straight arrows.
I don't want them mixed up
in anything, you know, sketchy.
- What's sketchy?
- I went to talk to Sonny Battaglia.
Oh?
Impressive man.
Knows how to get what he wants.
- He's a vicious scumbag.
- Yeah, he is.
Didn't speak too well of you either.
He seems to think you encouraged
Eddie to rat in the first place.
- That's not true.
- It's what he thinks.
And you know what he's like once
he gets that idea in his head. Stubborn.
He offered me a very sweet deal.
- What kind of deal?
- What kind of deal do you think?
You tell me.
You could make me
look good with the cops...
...and confess to what you've done...
...or you can make me look good
with Sonny Battaglia, and die.
That's your choice.
Die? You're a cop.
And cops never bend the law, do they?
Besides, I'm not even really a cop.
I'm just a consultant.
Looking out for number one.
Better make up your mind.
Battaglia's man is on his way.
I don't believe you.
Well, I'll call Sonny
and have him tell you himself.
You remember his voice, don't you?
Don't you?
- Yeah.
- Hey, Sonny.
- You again?
- Yeah, it's me again.
- Better be what I want.
- Remember that woman?
She's right here.
- Listen, you piece of dirt. You dog turd.
- Yeah, sure.
- When I get my hands...
- I'll put her on.
- Hello?
- You are dead. You hear me?
I am gonna rip off your head
and chew on your spine.
Nobody screws around with me
and lives. You hear me?
So, what's it gonna be, Gina?
Confess or die?
- You can't do this.
- Oh, I'm doing it.
Oh, he's here.
Faster than I thought.
There's no guns in the house.
The police have taken them all.
It's either him or me, Gina.
All right.
- All right. I did it, okay? I killed Eddie.
- Good. Tell me the details.
- You tell him to stop. Stop him!
- Details.
I followed them from work
Friday night. All right?
I watched them go to a motel.
Afterwards, she drove him to his car,
there was no one around.
I shot him.
Then I drove his body to a bridge,
and I dumped it over the edge.
Perfect. Thank you.
Agent Rigsby, arrest this woman.
Put your hands behind your back.
Looking good, sport. Looking good.
Knox wanted
to apologize to you personally...
- ...but she's still in the hospital.
- What is she gonna do now?
She's out of the marshal service,
of course.
She's gonna take some time off,
see what's next.
And, um...
...I wanna apologize too.
I got turned around,
and, uh, I was out of line.
And congratulations
on solving the case.
Come here. Give me a hug.
- Come on. There we go.
- Okay.
- You're a good man.
- All right.
Okay. Okay.
Um...
That's not how we do things in the
marshal's office, but I guess it works.
You two be well.
What were you thinking,
by the way? Unbelievable.
Believe, Lisbon. Believe.
Look at it this way.
We've closed yet another case.
Toying with mafia bosses
is no way to close cases. It's stupid.
You're just trying to find fault.
And I know why.
- Oh, really.
- You're grumpy about the present thing.
- Will you leave that alone?
- Oh, unbelievable.
You've got no reason
to be grumpy anymore.